

# **About Me**

# Corneliu Zediu

# Front-End Developer

Schwarenbergstraße 160 70184, Stuttgart

Phone: +49/15224019045

Mail: <a href="mailto:contact@corneliu-zediu.com">contact@corneliu-zediu.com</a>

Portfolio: <u>corneliu-zediu.com</u>
GitHub: <u>github.com/corneliuzediu</u>
LinkedIn: <u>linkedin.com/in/corneliuzediu</u>

I am a German-speaking Frontend Developer with experience in building web apps with JavaScript & Angular.

I started my IT journey coding Python and getting Python Certificates and then decided to get professional training and build complex projects and business apps. I have written projects alone and in teams including web apps, landing pages and OOP-based games based on clean code principles. You're welcome to visit my <u>public portfolio</u>,

I am looking forward to building on my experience and starting my career in IT in a junior developer position.

### Stack

Main Stack: - JavaScript

TypeScript, Angular

- HTML, CSS/SCSS, Bootstrap

Side Stack: - Git, APIs (REST), Google Firebase

### **Skills**

#### • JavaScript & Angular Application Development:

Cultivated experience in building landing pages, web apps, and object-oriented programming (OOP) based jump-and-run games using JavaScript and Angular.

#### • Software Team Collaboration:

Throughout my professional development, I actively participated in numerous group projects, gaining valuable experience in collaborating within software teams.

### • Strong Work Organization:

From retail experience I have developed effective work organization skills that directly apply to web development. Skilled in managing tasks, coordinating deadlines, and maintaining a well-structured workflow to ensure efficient project completion.

### **Professional Experience**

March 2019 - June 2022 Bielefeld & Stuttgart, Germany

Bershka Deutschland GmbH / Salesman & Chico Respo Bershka is a popular fashion retailer that offers trendy and affordable clothing and accessories for young men and women.

- Proficient collection, analysis and interpretation of KPIs in order to take the best data-driven decisions
- Effective guiding, training and support for the team members

November 2017 - June 2018 Bucharest, Romania

## Altius Fotovoltaics SRL / Economical Engineer

Altius is a manufacturer of photovoltaic panels with HQ in Bucharest and the factory in Giurgiu, Romania

• Efficiently operating and managing a wide range of industrial machinery and equipment with precision and expertise.

Summer 2014 - 2017 Sandusky, Ohio, USA

### **Cedar Point / General Area Supervisor**

Cedar Point, known as the "Roller Coaster Capital of the World," is a premier amusement park in Sandusky, Ohio.

• Efficiently configuring, managing and maintaining hardware components for optimal performance and functionality

#### Education

July 2022 - April 2023 Munich, Germany

### **Developer Akademie / Qualified Web-Developer Front-End**

Project based coding academy. Main Stack: JavaScript, Angular

Portfolio: www.corneliu-zediu.com

Extensive Coding School, Learning Front-End Development, Coding, Agile Project Management and building several projects in teams and alone.

February 2022 – now Stuttgart, Germany

### HarvardX CS50 / Certificate in Computer Science

#### **CS50's Introduction to Computer Science**

Relative topics include algorithms, data structure, software engineering, etc. Programming languages: C, Python, SQL, Javascript, CSS and HTML.

February 2022 - May 2022 Stuttgart, Germany

### **Python Institute OpenEDG** / Certificate in Python language

#### PCEP- Certified Entry-Level Python Programmer

The Course covers "Computer Programming Python Fundamentals", "Conditional Block and Loops" and "Data Collection".

### Languages

Romanian: native
English: fluent
German: very good